University Photograph; Collection ua390
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Two unidentified male students attending the 1971 State University of New York at Albany commencement ceremony., 1971 May 22
- A contact sheet containing images from the 1971 State University of New York at Albany commencement ceremony., 1971 May 22
- A contact sheet containing images of unidentified people attending an event associated with the 1971 State University of New York at Albany commencement ceremony., 1971 May 22
- Participating in the 1971 State University of New York at Albany commencement procession are, left to right: Phillip Sirotkin, executive vice president for academic affairs at the State University of New York at Albany from 1971 to 1976; Clifton C. Thorne, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1949, former Vice President of Student Affairs of the State University of New York at Albany; U.S. Senator Mark Hatfield; Louis T. Benezet, President of the State University of New York at Albany from July 1, 1970-June 30, 1975; and Harry S. Price, faculty member in the Department of History. Duplicate of 1290., 1971 May 22
- An unidentified man holding a trophy at an event associated with the 1971 State University of New York at Albany commencement ceremony. The original is mounted on a piece of matte board., 1971 May 22
- A State University of New York at Albany student showing a small boy and a teenage girl a film projector during Community-University Day, 1971., 1971 October 22
- Aerial photographof the University at Albany's uptown campus, ca. 1972
- Aerial photographof the University at Albany's uptown campus, ca. 1972
- Seth W. Spellman with students. Spellman was a Distinguished Service Professor and former dean of the School of Social Welfare. Spellman was also associated with the Allen (James E. Allen, Jr.) Collegiate Center, which was an experimental senior year of high school and freshman year of college combined, providing a Bachelor of Arts degree in three years. The center closed in 1976., 1972
- A picture of a sign for the State University of New York At Albany James E. Allen, Jr. Collegiate Center which was an experimental senior year of high school and freshman year of college combined, providing for a Bachelor of Arts degree in three years. The center closed in 1976., 1972
- A picture of a sign for the State University of New York At Albany James E. Allen, Jr. Collegiate Center which was an experimental senior year of high school and freshman year of college combined, providing for a Bachelor of Arts degree in three years. The center closed in 1976. The sign is posted outside of Brubacher Hall on the university's downtown campus., 1972
- A photograph of Seth W. Spellman with students. Spellman was a Distinguished Service Professor and former dean of the School of Social Welfare. Spellman was also associated with the Allen (James E. Allen, Jr.) Collegiate Center, which was an experimental senior year of high school and freshman year of college combined, providing a Bachelor of Arts degree in three years. The center closed in 1976., 1972
- A photograph of Seth W. Spellman with students. Spellman was a Distinguished Service Professor and former dean of the School of Social Welfare. Spellman was also associated with the Allen (James E. Allen, Jr.) Collegiate Center, which was an experimental senior year of high school and freshman year of college combined, providing a Bachelor of Arts degree in three years. The center closed in 1976., 1972
- A photograph of John Stutz teaching a class associated with the Allen (James E. Allen, Jr.) Collegiate Center, which was an experimental senior year of high school and freshman year of college combined, providing a Bachelor of Arts degree in three years. The center closed in 1976., 1972
- A picture of Tami Peterson, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1972, performing at the 1972 Telethon.
- A group photograph of the 1972-1973 State University of New York at Albany gymnastics team. Top, left to right: Allyson A. Bailey, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1976, captain; Karla Schlosser, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1972 and 1973; Susan Loevenguth; Bottom, left to right: Maryann Viskocil, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1975; Edith Cobane, coach; Jaqueline Kunkel, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1975. Original is mounted on a piece of matte board. Duplicate of 1989.
- A group of unidentified people attending an Ice Cream Social during Alumni Day, 1972. The event is taking place at the Campus Center Gardens on the uptown campus.
- A picture of unidentified people as they participate in the naming of scholarships during Alumni Day, 1972. A man and woman look at a plaque as those around them applaud. The event is taking place in one of the buildings on the uptown campus.
- A group of unidentified alumni attending an Ice Cream Social during Alumni Day, 1972. The event is taking place at the Campus Center Gardens on the uptown campus.
- A photograph of members of the 1972-1973 State University of New York at Albany football team during a game. This photograph appeared in the Torch, 1973.
- A group portrait of the 1972 State University of New York at Albany football team and coaches.
- William G. Floyd, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1954, and State University of New York at Albany Alumni Association President at the time of this event, participating in an event on Alumni Day, 1972.
- A photograph of the Old Wazoo Band performing at an Ice Cream Social during Alumni Day, 1972.
- Aerial view of the Uptown Campus and immediate vicinity, scale: 1" = 1000'., 1972
- A photo of unidentified adults and children looking at booths with travel information during Community-University Day. The event is taking place in a building on the uptown campus at the State University of New York at Albany., 1972
- State University of New York at Albany faculty members in the Community Relations Office are, left to right: Robert H. Rice, Jr.; Edith Hardy Leet, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1966, Nathalie E. Lampman, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1965, and H. David Van Dyck, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1955., 1972
- Werner Kolln, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1973, receiving the Chancellor's Award of Scholar-Athlete for 1971-1972. Pictured, left to right, are: John Quattrochi, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1974; Richard "Doc" Sauers, basketball coach; Werner Kolln, and Reggie Smith.
- Students graduating from the Educational Opportunities Program attending the 1971 State University of New York at Albany commencement ceremony include: James Bouldin, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1972, Lucy M. Bouldin, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1973, Willye M. Neal, and Audrey E. Devries, both State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1972.
- A picture of William G. Floyd, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1954 and State University of New York at Albany Alumni Association President at the time of this event, presenting the Distinguished Alumni Award to Edna S. Schafer MacAffer, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1924, on Alumni Day, 1972.
- Clifton C. Thorne, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1949 and former Vice President of Student Affairs of the State University of New York at Albany and his family with Louis Benezet. Louis T. Benezet was the President of the State University of New York at Albany from July 1, 1970-June 30, 1975., 1972
- A picture of William G. Floyd (viewer's right), New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1954 and State University of New York at Albany Alumni Association President at the time of this event, as he receives a commemorative plaque from Timothy J. Maroney, Jr. of the Approach 13-30 Corporation for the Alumni Association's participation in the Nutshell Program, winter 1972. There are crop marks on two sides of the photograph.
- William Floyd, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1954 and State University of New York at Albany Alumni Association President at the time of this event, presents the first Citizen of the University Award to Samuel E. Aronowitz, President of the Benevolent Association, during an event on Alumni Day, 1972. The event is taking place in a building on the uptown campus.
- Students graduating from the Educational Opportunities Program attending the 1971 State University of New York at Albany commencement ceremony include: James Bouldin, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1972, Lucy M. Bouldin, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1973, Willye M. Neal, and Audrey E. Devries, both State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1972.
- A picture of Dr. Melvin I. Urofsky with a student, circa 1972. Urofsky was with the Department of Innovative and Developmental Education and was the department's Assitant Dean for the 1971-1972 academic year.
- John Stutz teaching a business class (with the use of a computer) associated with the Allen (James E. Allen, Jr.) Collegiate Center, which was an experimental senior year of high school and freshman year of college combined, providing a Bachelor of Arts degree in three years. The center closed in 1976., 1972
- Pictured in the Campus Center Lobby at the State University of New York at Albany is the Promotional Agenda Commmittee publicizing an upcoming visit to Albany by George S. McGovern and Senator Edward Moore Kennedy during their campaign for the Presidential and Vice Presidential offices., 1972
- Pictured in the Campus Center Lobby at the State University of New York at Albany are unidentified students visiting the Promotional Agenda Commmittee table publicizing an upcoming visit to Albany by George S. McGovern and Senator Edward Moore Kennedy during their campaign for the Presidential and Vice Presidential offices., 1972
- Louis T. Benezet, President of the State University of New York at Albany from July 1, 1970-June 30, 1975, at a party, apparently receiving a toast. He is in the lower righthand corner of the photograph, wearing a white coat., 1972
- A portrait of the 1972-1973 State University of New York at Albany women's basketbal team. Front row, left to right: Marsha Collins; Donna DeLucco, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1973; Olive (Ollie) Simon, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1975; Diane Fassett, row 2: Elsa Gorordo; Jane Sper; Kay Sands; Judy Joseph; Barbara Brody, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1975; Esther Hammes; Vernita McCormick, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1978, row 3: Mary Beck, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1974 and manager of the team, and Barbara Palm, coach. Duplicate of 5759.
- Louis T. Benezet, President of the State University of New York at Albany from July 1, 1970-June 30, 1975, speaking at a memorial service for the 11 Israeli athletes killed in the 1972 Olympic Games in Munich, Germany. The photograph was used in the 1973 "Torch," the school's yearbook.
- Louis T. Benezet, President of the State University of New York at Albany from July 1, 1970-June 30, 1975, speaking at a memorial service for the 11 Israeli athletes killed at the 1972 Olympic Games in Munich, West Germany. The photograph was used in the 1973 "Torch," the school's yearbook.
- Students graduating from the Educational Opportunities Program attending the 1971 State University of New York at Albany commencement ceremony include: second from viewer's right, James Bouldin, and third from right, Willye M. Neil, both State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1972. Duplicate of 1231.
- State University of New York at Albany faculty members in the Community Relations Office are, left to right: Robert H. Rice, Jr.; Edith Hardy Leet, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1966, Nathalie E. Lampman, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1965, and H. David Van Dyck, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1955., 1972
- Students graduating from the Educational Opportunities Program attending the 1971 State University of New York at Albany commencement ceremony include: second from viewer's right, James Bouldin, and third from right, Willye M. Neil, both State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1972. Duplicate of 1234.
- Students holding a banner in a procession for Torch Night, 1972.
- Unidentified nurses and students of the University at Albany giving and taking blood., 1972
- Seth W. Spellman with students. Spellman was also a Distinguished Service Professor and former dean of the School of Social Welfare. Spellman was associated with the Allen (James E. Allen, Jr.) Collegiate Center, which was an experimental senior year of high school and freshman year of college combined, providing a Bachelor of Arts degree in three years. The center closed in 1976., 1972
- Paul Raskin's class associated with the Allen (James E. Allen, Jr.) Collegiate Center, which was an experimental senior year of high school and freshman year of college combined, providing a Bachelor of Arts degree in three years. The center closed in 1976. Raskin is out of view in this picture., 1972
- The Cantus Infirmus performing a work of P.D.Q. BACH for the television airing of the State University of New York at Albany Telethon, 1972. P.D.Q. Bach is considered not to be a pseudonym, but rather a character that Peter Schickele, composer, musician, author, and satirist, has created.
- Group photo of women's tennis team. Coach is Peggy Mann. The player at the bottom left is Linda (Lynn) Gabriel., 1972
- A picture of Grenfell N. Rand, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1934, Augusta Katz Biskin, New York State College for Teachers, Class of 1936, dressed as Minerva, and Louis T. Benezet, President of the State University of New York at Albany from July 1, 1970-June 30, 1975, at an event during Alumni Day, 1972. The event is taking place in a building on the uptown campus.
- A group of unidentified people attending an Ice Cream Social during Alumni Day, 1972. The event is taking place at the Campus Center Gardens on the uptown campus.
- Pictured in the Campus Center Lobby at the State University of New York at Albany are unidentified students visiting the Promotional Agenda Commmittee table publicizing an upcoming visit to Albany by George S. McGovern and Senator Edward Moore Kennedy during their campaign for the Presidential and Vice Presidential offices., 1972
- Informational booths with travel information during Community-University Day. The event is taking place in a building on the uptown campus at the State University of New York at Albany. Part of a second image is visible in the right margin of the original., 1972
- Unidentified students walking on the Academic Podium at the Uptown Campus., 1972
- A portrait of Anis Phillips, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1973, in what appears to be a nurse's uniform., 1972-1973
- Unidentified students and staff members at the Campus Center Snack Bar at the State University of New York at Albany., 1972 April
- Several unidentified people purchasing food from employees at the Snack Bar in the Campus Center at the State University of New York at Albany., 1972 April
- A group of unidentified people purchasing items at the Campus Center snack bar at the State University of New York at Albany while an employee provides service., 1972 April
- A picture of several unidentified students playing a game of pool in the Campus Center Pool Room at the State University of New York at Albany., 1972 April
- Unidentified people on the Campus Center staircase between the lobby and the cafeteria at the State University of New York at Albany on the uptown campus., 1972 April
- Article by John Fairhall "E. D. Stone talks about Albany State". Edward Durell Stone, architect for the State University of New York at Albany Uptown Campus, discusses his design. Writing in the right top margin includes "ASP" and "April 2, 1972"., 1972 April 2
- Opening ceremony of the Allen (James E. Allen, Jr.) Collegiate Center, which was an experimental senior year of high school and freshman year of college combined, providing a Bachelor of Arts degree in three years. The center closed in 1976. The opening was held in Brubacher Hall in August 1972. The photograph is from the Tower Tribune newspaper (vol. 4, no. 2) of September 5, 1972. The photo depicts a row of dramatic, Palladian-like windows and there are registration marks in the (upper) left and the (lower) right margins., 1972 August
- A picture of actress Jane Fonda, a visiting speaker to the institution, September 15, 1972. At the time, Fonda was an ardent protestor against the United States' involvement in the Vietnam War. There are crop marks and in the right margin is noted, "6-B K-WUT FRI 2Col x 3 3/4 inches.", 1972 September 15
- Unidentified people standing by a man sitting at a typewriter during Community-University Day 1972 at the State University of New York at Albany., 1972 October 21
- A sign welcoming visitors to Community-University Day at the State University of New York at Albany on the uptown campus. The sign says "Community-University Open House, October 21, 1972, Public Welcome." One of the quadrangles can be seen in the background., 1972 October 21
- A library exhibition during Community-University Day 1972 called "The Book: From Author to Reader, A Library Odyssey." The photographer's stamp is in the bottom margin., 1972 October 21
- Unidentified people looking at the library exhibition during Community-University Day, 1972. The photographer's stamp is in the bottom margin., 1972 October 21
- A contact sheet containing images of the University Library, a library exhibition, and people attending Community-University 1972 at the State University of New York at Albany., 1972 October 21
- Pictured attending Community-University Day 1972 at the State University of New York are: Albany, New York Mayor Erastus Corning, front left; Frank J. Duci of Schenectady, second from left behind Corning; Millie Van Straub and J. Vanderbilt Straub at the foot of the staircase., 1972 October 21
- Jan C. Eisenberg, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1976, leading a tour during Community- University Day, 1972, on the uptown campus. Duplicate of 9271., 1972 October 21
- Unidentified people looking at the library exhibition during Community-University Day, 1972., 1972 October 21
- Unidentified women looking at the library exhibition during Community-University Day, 1972. The photographer's stamp is in the bottom margin., 1972 October 21
- Jan C. Eisenberg, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1976, leading a tour during Community-University Day, 1972, on the uptown campus. Duplicate of 4178. There are crop marks in the bottom and right margins., 1972 October 21
- Louis T. Benezet, President of the State University of New York at Albany from July 1, 1970-June 30, 1975, and J.Vanderbilt Straub, chairman of the University Council, presenting a "Key to the University" to Albany Mayor Erastus Corning and Schenectady Mayor Frank Duci during Community-University Day 1973 at the State University of New York at Albany. Community-University Day was introduced to encourage internation between the campus and the city., 1972 October 21
- Ethiopian legislators visit Albany to observe the State Legislature. Pictured left to right are: Deputy Mewail; Senator Fetur; Deputy Abebe; James J. Heaphey of the Comparative Development Studies Center at the State University of New York at Albany; Deputy Paulos; and Andrew M. Miner, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1972, graduate student., 1972 November
- Three images the State University of New York at Albany men's basketball team playing against Brockport. The images appeared in The Torch, 1973.
- A portrait of Bruce J. Cummings, football player for the State University of New York at Albany football team in 1973.
- A portrait of Frank Villanova, football player for the State University of New York at Albany football team in 1973.
- A portrait of Ron Gardner, football player for the State University of New York at Albany football team in 1973.
- A portrait of Arnold J. Will, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1975, and football player for the State University of New York at Albany football team in 1973.
- Recipients of the Civil Service Merit Award: Elmer Wicke, fireman; Julian Podolec, maintenance aide; John Hartley; Henry Pietaszewski, dormitory maintenance foreman; John DeSorbo, supervising janitor., 1973
- A photograph of spectators and coaches watching a basketball game. Richard "Doc" Sauers is sittting in the foreground. This image appeared in The Torch, 1973.
- A portrait of Michael J. Basla, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1975 and member of the football team in 1973.
- Louis T. Benezet, President of the State University of New York at Albany from July 1, 1970-June 30, 1975, and New York Mayor Erastus Corning participating in an event during Community-University Day 1973.
- An official portrait (#2) of Louis T. Benezet, President of the State University of New York at Albany from July 1, 1970-June 30, 1975., 1973
- An official portrait (#8) of Louis T. Benezet, President of the State University of New York at Albany from July 1, 1970-June 30, 1975., 1973
- An official portrait (#9) of Louis T. Benezet, President of the State University of New York at Albany from July 1, 1970-June 30, 1975., 1973
- A portrait of William (Bill) L. Adams, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1973, football player for the State University of New York at Albany, 1973.
- A portrait of Jeffrey T. O'Donnell, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1974, and football player for the State University of New York at Albany football team in 1973.
- A portrait of Vincent E. Pierce, University of New York at Albany, Class of 1974, football player for the State University of New York at Albany, 1973.
- A portrait of Rudolph E. Vido, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1978 and football player for the State University of New York at Albany football team in 1973.
- A portrait of Mike Inco, football player for the State University of New York at Albany football team in 1973.
- A portrait of Thomas B. Taylor, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1977 and member of the football team in 1973.
- A portrait of Tim Myers, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1975, and football player for the State University of New York at Albany football team in 1973.
- A picture of a small group of visitors to campus, standing on the Academic Podium of the uptown campus, next to the pool and fountain., 1973
- Domnick M. Pagano, State University of New York at Albany, Class of 1975 and member of the football team in 1973.
- A collage of images from the Torch yearbook showing the various activities of the 1973 State University of New York at Albany Telethon event.
- An official portrait (#3) of Louis T. Benezet, President of the State University of New York at Albany from July 1, 1970-June 30, 1975., 1973
- An official portrait (#5) of Louis T. Benezet, President of the State University of New York at Albany from July 1, 1970-June 30, 1975., 1973
- An official portrait (#15) of Louis T. Benezet, President of the State University of New York at Albany from July 1, 1970-June 30, 1975., 1973
- An official portrait (#16) of Louis T. Benezet, President of the State University of New York at Albany from July 1, 1970-June 30, 1975., 1973
- A portrait of Johnny C. Cage, Jr., fullback for the State University of New York at Albany football team in 1973.